回到大自然的感觉真好
It's nice to get back to nature.
我真该多多这么做
Why don't I do this more often?
这森林真美
What a beautiful forest.
你好呀  小蝴蝶
Hello, little butterfly.
你叫什么...
What's your na...
你在干嘛
Whatcha doing?
我刚沉浸在虚拟现实的乐趣中
I was enjoying some virtual reality,
而你这张现实的大脸把我拉了出来
until you ruined it with your actual face.
这是什么味儿
What am I smelling?
这是汽车香片
Oh, it's car air freshener.
我在模拟森林的味道
I was simulating the smell of the forest.
真正的森林可不是这个味儿
That's not what the forest smells like.
我咋知道
Well, how would I know?
你干嘛意淫自己在户外
Why are you pretending to be outdoors?
你又不喜欢
You hate it.
艾米给我看了一个有说服力的研究
Amy showed me a compelling study
研究证实花点时间待在野外
that demonstrated the cognitive benefit
对认知能力有好处
of spending time in the wilderness.
伙计  只要你想
Buddy, I am ready to drive you
我随时都可以开车载你去野外
into the wilderness any time you want
然后把你扔那儿
and leave you there.
随便你笑  但部分参与者
Well, make your jokes, but some of the participants
远离所有科技  在树林待了四天后
who spent four days in the woods away from all technology
记录指出  回来后逻辑思维能力提高了50%
reported a 50% gain in reasoning skills upon their return.
好吧  如果那是真的
Okay, if that's true,
为什么没有出现更多的天才松鼠
why aren't there more genius squirrels?
你可能比我更需要这个
You may need this more than I do.
你的茶泡好了
Here's your tea.
不要悄悄走近一个坐在圆木上的男人
Do not sneak up on a guy when he's sitting on a log.
如果你真的那么想亲近大自然
You know, if you really want to be in nature,
我们何不去租一个小木屋
why don't we rent a cabin?
抱歉  你啥时候来的  我都没...
Look, I'm sorry, when did you even get here? I...
有个跟我有业务往来的医生
You know, there's a cabin in Big Bear
一直邀我去大熊湖那的一个小木屋
that a doctor I work with keeps offering me.
因为那男的想勾搭你吗
Because he's hitting on you?
女的
She.
那就好
Oh, good.
但我男女通杀
But I could get her.
我们周末可以一起去
We could all go for the weekend.
一定会很好玩
It'll be fun.
好吧  借过
Yeah... Excuse me.
查"好玩"这个词  再跟我谈
Here, look up "Fun", get back to me.
咱俩可以去好好过个周末啊
You and I could still go and have a nice weekend.
好啊
Sure.
去嘛  谢尔顿  我们也去
Come on, Sheldon, let's go with them.
我不要
I hardly think so.
你们一定要跟以下生物问好
You be sure and say hello to
蚊子  蜜蜂  熊  蛇
all the mosquitoes, bees, bears, snakes,
负鼠  毒葛
possums, poison oak,
最后  也是最重要的是
oh, and last, but not least,
玩吉他的少男少女们
teenagers with guitars.
我问问能不能出借
I'll see if it's available.
如果那个研究是真的
You know, if that study's real,
莱纳德回来后可能就会比你聪明哦
Leonard might come back smarter than you.
-你这是在逼我就范吗  -是的
- Are you trying to manipulate me? - Yes.
干得好  很成功  我们去
Well done, it worked, we're going.
好棒
Yay!
别这样  拉杰
Come on, Raj,
让我帮你拿个袋吧
give me a bag.
不行  你有孕在身
No, no, you're pregnant.
你的力气要用来
The only thing you carry
"帮"人类孕育美好明天的希望
is our hope for a better tomorrow.
你去哪儿了
Hey, where you been?
拉杰载我去看产科医生
Uh, Raj took me to the baby doctor
然后我们顺便去了一趟杂货店
and then we swung by the grocery store.
你有买全麦饼干吗
Did you get graham crackers?
我是说  宝宝还好吗
I mean, are... what... is the baby okay?
买了  很好
Yes and yes.
我不知道你今天办事需要帮忙
I didn't know you needed help running errands today.
不用啊  但拉杰主动来帮忙
I didn't, but Raj volunteered.
是吗
Really?
是啊  自从你告诉他我怀孕后
Yeah, ever since you told him I was pregnant,
他对我真是呵护备至
he's really been making a fuss over me.
这样也挺好的
Oh. Well, I guess that's kind of sweet.
妮妮  我刚给你转发了一张
Bernie, I just forwarded you a list
洛杉矶前五位哺乳专家的名单
of the top five lactation consultants in Los Angeles.
虽然我有最爱的人选
I know my favorite,
但我还是想听听你的意见
but I'd love to hear what you think.
突然开始变味了
And it just got weird.
艾米在楼下了
Hey. Amy's downstairs.
好的  马上走
Okay, one sec.
你头上戴的是什么
Uh, what-what you got goin' on here?
我买了一顶棒球帽
I bought a baseball cap.
我看出来了
I can see that.
帽子是哪个球队呀
What team did you get?
《哈利波特》的赫奇帕奇学院
Uh, Hufflepuff, from Harry Potter.
去森林戴啥帽子呀
Well, we'll be in the woods.
我可以走了
I'm ready to go.
你有什么话想要对他说吗
Anything you'd like to say to him?
谢尔顿  帽子不错
Nice hat, Sheldon.
谢谢
Thanks.
你干嘛就欺负我
Why are you so mean to me?
你到底在看什么啊
What the hell are you watching?
拉杰在网上找了这些生孩子的视频
Raj found all these childbirth videos online.
这是一个女人在河里生孩子
This one is of a woman giving birth in a river.
好吧  那是我这辈子见过
Okay, that is the least Jewish thing
最不犹太风的事情了
I've ever seen in my life.
你不觉得拉杰对宝宝的事
You feel like Raj is getting a little carried away
有点过于上心吗
with all the baby stuff?
不觉得啊
I don't think so.
他只是想要参与进来而已
He just wants to be part of the experience.
好吧  你说是就是吧
All right, if you say so.
盒子里是什么
What's in the box?
是一个超声波麦克风
Oh, it's an ultrasonic microphone
用它可以听到宝宝的心跳
so we can hear the baby's heartbeat.
挺酷啊
That's cool.
我们能试试吗
Can we try it?
那个其实是拉杰订的
Actually, Raj ordered it.
他让我保证会等到他来了再用
He made me promise to wait till he was here.
这样他才能...
So he can be...
参与进来吗
part of the experience?
是啊
Yeah.
真惊讶他居然让我们单独"受孕"
I'm surprised he let us conceive without him.
这是他痛处  别在他面前提
It's a sore spot-- don't bring it up.
好有爱  好有乡村气息
It's so cute and rustic up here.
对啊
I know.
你有看到他们还有录影带出租店吗
Did you see they still have a video rental place?
好像弗州的威廉斯堡历史保护区
it's like Colonial Williamsburg.
手机信号只剩下一格了
Well...cell service is down to one bar,
如果有人需要找医生
so if anyone needs medical attention
或者告诉陌生人  他的政治观点很智障
or to tell a stranger their political views are stupid,
赶紧趁现在
now's the time.
你有彻底断过网吗
Have you ever been off the grid before?
有过一次
Once.
是在我的手机没电
The battery ran out on my phone.
得等我的iPad开机的那段时间
I had to wait for my iPad to turn on.
那次我以为他要把我生吞活剥了
I was afraid he was gonna eat me.
拉杰到了
Raj just pulled up.
我得跟他说说这事
I'm gonna say something to him.
别说了  他一番好意
Leave it alone. He means well.
所以你不觉得他需要稍微有点分寸吗
So you don't think he needs to rein it in a little?
不用  没觉得
No, not really.
你不担心他表现得有点像
And you're not concerned he's acting like
你肚子里的也是他孩子吗
somehow this is his kid, too?
他只是给予我关爱和支持
He's just trying to be supportive.
单纯关爱和支持
Just supportive.
完全没越界也不过火吗
Not over-the-top in any way?
是的
No.
大家安安啊
Hello!
此熊是美国零售商Costco出的巨熊
2.6米高  含外送费只要280美元
你早就看见他拿着这个了
You saw him carrying that.
宇航员都看见了
Astronauts saw him carrying that.
这地方好棒
This place is great!
那个医生真好  就白白借你用了
So nice of that doctor to just let you use it.
她要带我去看拉拉女团的演唱会
Well, she is taking me to an Indigo Girls concert,
话先别说太早
so hold that thought.
好
Okay.
我们要互相检查有没有虱子了吗
Should we check each other for ticks?
谢尔顿  就下车走进屋这段路而已
Sheldon, all we did was walk in from the car.
随你便
Oh. Well, suit yourself.
谁想检查我身上
Who wants to check me?
不过  不怕一万只怕万一嘛
On the other hand, safety first.
大雨大雨一直下
Wow, it's really coming down.
真是衰透了
This sucks.
踏青是没戏了
And there goes our hike.
太"失望"了
Oh, not our hike!
现在我们只能保持安全与暖和了
Now we have to stay safe and warm.
我们还是能去啊
You know, we could still go.
一点小雨也不会死人
A little rain isn't gonna kill us.
你跟谢尔顿在雨中出去过吗
Have you been outside in the rain with Sheldon?
-没  -你会祈求雨能弄死你
- No. - You'll wish it would kill you.
我们现在干嘛
So what do we do now?
这里有些桌游啊
They have some board games.
大多数的叠叠乐积木都不见了
Eh, most of the Jenga pieces are missing
而拼字游戏只剩七个字母砖
and the Scrabble only has seven tiles,
除非你想叠一个看起来很垃圾的塔
so unless you want to build an unimpressive structure
外加"SHNERPF"字样在一旁  否则拉倒吧
with the word "SHNERPF" next to it, move on.
我们来生火吧
Hey, let's light a fire.
感觉好舒服
Ooh, that sounds cozy.
我好像没有生过真的火
I don't think I've lit a real fire before.
只是很基础的热力学
Ah, it's basic thermodynamics.
我们俩肯定能搞定
I'm sure we can figure that out.
我可以把木头按圆锥状叠来促进空气流动
I could stack the logs conically to facilitate airflow.
这的确能为燃烧提供最足的氧气
That would maximize oxygen for optimal combustion.
对  所以我们只需要...
Right. So all we need is to...
搞定
Got it.
生火装置是科学家发明的
A scientist made that.
拉杰  你是我全世界最好的朋友
Look, Raj, you're my best friend in the world
我也很感谢你对这孩子这么上心
and I really appreciate your enthusiasm about the baby.
别客气  我的荣幸
Please, my pleasure.
我跟华仔也很愿意让你全程参与进来
And, of course, Howie and I both want you to be a part of all this.
但我们得设一些界线
But we have to set some boundaries.
我不懂了
I don't understand.
这孩子不是我们三个人的
The three of us aren't having this baby.
是我们两个人的
Just the two of us.
好  我懂了
Okay. Yeah, I get it.
我不乱插手了
I'll back off.
谢谢你能理解
Thanks for understanding.
那当然
Of course.
我给你们留点空间吧
I'll give you guys some space.
帮你们把这玩意弄走  别碍事了
Let me just get this out of your way.
你需要帮忙吗
You need some help?
不用  我能行
No, I got it.
拉杰  拉杰  等等
Raj... Raj, wait.
别说了  伯纳黛特
Please, Bernadette.
让我带着最后一点尊严离去吧
Let me leave with my dignity.
你们想玩一个喝酒游戏吗
Hey, you guys want to play a drinking game?
那啥...我们根本赢不了啊
Oh, well now, well now, we'll never win.
这项活动你老玩
You always play the drinking game.
不是"喝酒"这游戏  是喝酒玩的游戏
Not the drinking game, a drinking game.
说句公道话  两种她都是高手
To be fair, good at both.
怎么玩
What's the game?
好  这个游戏叫"我从未做过"
All right, it's called Never Have I Ever.
规则特别简单
The rules are simple.
每人说一件自己从未做过的事
Someone says something they've never done,
但其他人谁做过  谁就得喝酒
but if you have done it, you take a drink.
我从未玩过这个游戏
I've never played that before.
等一下
Hey, now, wait.
我们已经开始了吗  我需要喝酒吗
Have we started? Do I drink?
-到底怎么回事  -好了
- What is happening? - Okay.
冷静一点  我先来
Calm down. I'll go first.
好  我看看啊
All right, let's see.
我从未...
Never have I ever...
她正在努力回想一件她没做过的事
She's trying to think of something she's never done before.
这够她想好久了
This could take a while.
好好笑哦
Very funny.
我从未...
Okay, never have I ever...
算了吧
Yeah, you know what?
还是先从你们开始吧
Let's just circle back.
好的  我先来
Okay, I'll go.
我从未被逮捕过
Never have I ever been arrested.
那我就得喝了
So I drink.
不  只有你做过才需要喝
No, it's only if you've done it.
懂了
Got it.
真不敢相信你居然被逮捕过
I can't believe you've been arrested.
我还不敢相信佩妮没被逮捕过呢
I can't believe Penny hasn't.
谢尔顿  你犯了什么事啊
Sheldon, what did you do?
这不是一件值得骄傲的事
Well, I'm not proud of it,
不过
but...
我曾经乱穿马路
I jaywalked.
我的妈呀  这不就跟恐怖片一样吗
Oh, no, it's like a horror movie.
我们和一个疯子一起困在小木屋里
We're trapped in a cabin with a maniac.
我真惊讶你居然做了这种事
I'm surprised you would do that.
我从街道的中间乱穿的
No, I crossed in the middle of the street.
通常情况下  我不会做这种事
And normally, I wouldn't,
但我看见了一个虎视眈眈的女童子军
but I saw an aggressive-looking Girl Scout,
当时又恰逢女童军饼干销售旺季
and it was the heart of cookie season.
总之  路边站了一个警察
Anyway, there was a police officer,
他目睹了整个过程
and he witnessed the whole thing.
什么  他就为了这个逮捕你吗
What-- he arrested you for that?
不  他什么也没做
No, he didn't do anything.
于是我说  "你刚才看见
So I said, "You just saw me jaywalk.
我乱穿马路了  你是白吃干饭的吗"
Why aren't you doing your job?" You know?
"也许我应该以
"M-Maybe I should arrest you
冒充警察罪逮捕你才对"
for-for impersonating a police officer."
然后你就被逮捕了
And then you got arrested.
这也是我被逮捕的原因
Oh, and how.
我觉得自己犯了一个大错
I feel like I just made a horrible mistake.
没错
Yeah.
不过从另一方面来说
But on the other hand,
我又不是要跟他断绝来往
I didn't kick him out of our lives.
我不过让他别太越界而已
I just asked him to back off a little.
没错
Yeah.
怎么了  你要哭了吗
What? Are you gonna cry?
没错
Yeah!
你这是孕期荷尔蒙作祟  还是真的很难过啊
Is it baby hormones or actually sad?
我自己也分不出来
I can't tell anymore!
我马上去找他
I'll go get him.
把熊熊也带回来
And bring back the bear!
这个游戏太危险了
This game's dangerous.
我轻轻松松就能让你惹上麻烦
I could get you in trouble.
此话怎讲
How?
我从未
Well, never have I ever
用谢尔顿的牙刷来刷水槽
used Sheldon's toothbrush to clean the sink.
好呀  你想这么玩是吧
Fine, is that how you want to play this?
很好  我从未
All right, never have I ever come up
给自己的生殖器取过小名
with a nickname for my own genitals.
我就不该把《鼠来宝》那三只的名字告诉你
Never should've told you about Alvin and the Chipmunks.
好了  该我了
Okay. My turn.
我从未...
Never have I ever
让我女友在床上爽歪歪
completely rocked my girlfriend's world in bed.
艾米...
Amy...
你懂规则的啦
You know the rules.
喝吧
Drink.
你也喝吧
Yeah, go ahead.
正是小爷
That's right.
好了  该我了
All right, my turn.
我知道了
Oh, I know.
我从未因为觉得我老婆不善理财
Never have I ever kept a secret bank account,
而有一个放私房钱的银行账号
because I think my wife can't handle money.
我赢了吗
Did I win?
我觉得好像是我赢了
I feel like I won.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
你知道我赚得比你多对吧
You realize I make more money than you?
我不是  我知道  但可有啥关系啊
I don't, I know, but this isn't a big deal.
我不过是私下存了点小钱嘛
It's just a little savings I put aside.
我们已经结婚了
We're married.
我们应该分享一切
We're supposed to share everything.
你是指  分享你的巨额信用卡账单吗
What-- you mean, like, your massive credit card debt?
我要宣布了
I'm calling it.
我赢了
I won.
我很感激你来道歉
I appreciate the apology,
但这真的没有必要
but it's really not necessary.
是我过界了
I overstepped my bounds.
不  拉杰  你做得很棒
No, Raj, you've been great.
但我也需要开始承担我的那部分责任了
I just, I need to start doing my part around here.
本宫听到了
I hear that.
如果是这样的话
Well, if that's the case,
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
is there anything I can do to help?
目前没有
Well, not right now.
不过我们可以试试你给我们买的麦克风
But we could try out that microphone you got us,
听听孩子的心跳
and listen to the baby's heartbeat.
真的吗
Really?
我可以跟你们一起听吗
It's okay if I listen with you?!
当然了
Of course.
那我能往你的肚肚上射超声波胶吗
Can I squirt the ultrasound jelly on your stomach?
瞧瞧啊
Hey, look at that.
又开始变味了
It's weird again.
好的  你完全有权生气
Okay, you have every right to be mad.
你说的也是实话
And what you said is true.
你确实赚得比我多
You do make more money than me.
我没有权做出那种事
So I had no right to do what I did.
真的很对不起
And I'm so sorry.
希望你能原谅我
I hope you can forgive me.
这个秘密账户你有了多久
How long have you had this secret account?
有几年了  但只是每个月存上几块钱
A couple years, but I just put a few bucks aside
以备不时之需
every month for emergencies.
你存了多少钱
Well, how much you got in there?
6427美元
$6,427.
等奶奶给我的20块生日红包到了  就6447了
$47 once my nana's birthday check gets here.
天啊  莱纳德  你知道
My God, Leonard, do you know
这么一笔钱我能拿来干嘛吗
what I could do with that kind of money?
我知道  所以我才藏起来了
No, I do, and that's why I hid it.
你要是不用  这钱有什么意义
What good is it if you don't use it?
你有你爱但是从不穿的鞋
Uh, uh, you have shoes you love, but never wear.
而我有我爱
I have money I love,
但从来不花的钱啊
but never spend.
我们俩还真是天造地设的一对呢
We're kind of a cute couple that way.
再次说声对不起
Again, I'm sorry.
我不应该瞒着你的
I shouldn't have kept it a secret.
其实我也有没告诉你的秘密
Well, I have a secret I've been keeping from you, too.
是秘密银行账户吗
Is it a secret bank account?
因为那就太棒了
Because that would be awesome.
我恨我的工作
I hate my job.
真的吗
Really?
为什么
Why?
为了卖药而跟医生调情  感觉特别不好
Because I don't feel good flirting with doctors for sales.
虽然我确实挣了很多钱
I mean, I know I make a lot of money.
但我已经不开心很长一段时间了
But I haven't been happy for a while.
那你为什么不告诉我呢
Why didn't you tell me?
因为我知道你有多在乎
Because I know how important it is to you
我能取得一些成绩
that I'm having some success.
不是这样的
That's not true.
真的吗  那么我回去当演员
Okay, really? So you'd be fine if I went
当服务员  你也不介意吗
back to acting and waiting tables again?
如果那是你想做的事  我不介意
If that's what you want to do, yes.
那不是我想做的事
Well, it's not what I want to do.
太好了
Oh, yes.
我想要什么并不重要
Doesn't matter what I want.
这份工作能让我还清卡债
Look, this job is gonna get me out of debt.
我就会做成年人该做的事  坚持到底
So I'm gonna do the grown-up thing and see it through.
那确实是成年人的行为
Well, that is the grown-up thing.
大概吧
I guess.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
话说
You know,
我从未
never have I ever made love
在雨天的森林中做过爱
in the forest while it was raining.
看来该我去喝酒了
Well, guess I gotta drink.
好了  准备开始
All right, here we go.
我什么都没听到
I'm not hearing anything.
等一下
Well, give me a second.
你确定你能做好吗
Are you sure you can do this?
是谁用金属探测器
Hey, who found four dollars and change
在沙滩里找到过四块多美元的钢镚
on the beach with his metal detector?
是我埋的  好让我们能回家
I buried it there, so we could go home.
等等  听到了
Wait, that's it.
这简直是最美好的事情了
Isn't that the best?
你们造了个人
You guys made a person.
是的
We did.
我感觉我也有帮到忙
And I like to think I helped.
你没有
You didn't.
我从未
Oh, um, never have I ever
喝过过期的牛奶
drunk milk past its expiration date.
我从未
Never have I ever
取消过牙医预约
cancelled a dentist appointment.
我从未
Oh, uh, never have I ever
把脚伸进过大海
put my foot in the ocean.
我从未
Never have I ever
路上看见喜欢的东西就按喇叭
honked if I liked anything.
我从未
Uh... never have I ever
扔出  接到或碰过飞盘
thrown, caught or touched a Frisbee.
我从未
Never have I ever
在尝过我的食物之前
put salt on my food
就开始撒盐
without trying it first.
我从未
Never have I ever
把电梯里的所有按钮都按了过
pushed all the buttons in an elevator.
谁没有黑历史啊
Well, we all have a past.